my name is mang and I'm in my barber
shop today we're going to be doing a
little different video today I've been
getting a lot of questions about how to
style your hair with what product and
For What occasion so I have three
products here all by American Crew this
is the Pomade this is the fiber and
um we have the foaming cream this is
totally not a paid advertisement by
American Crew I just happen to have
their product on hand three different
kinds of products I know right and so
that's where we're going to be working
with today now if you want me to review
or check out a different product please
drop it in the comments below and I'll
see what I can do all right let's get to
it so this is my hair by default when
you wash and dry everything just falls
down and it lays just like a bowl cut
first product that I'm going to be
reviewing is the Pomade one just because
I think it's the easiest one to wash out
and restyle for the next one and then
most likely I'm going to be doing the
fiber last just because I think it's the
hardest one out of all three to wash out
right
so
Pomade is a medium hold with a high
shine meaning that it is very
shiny when you put it on almost looks
like it's wet
um I the occasion I would put this on if
I have like my leather jacket on it
would look like a something like a
Greaser or from Grease lining or
something like that uh maybe like
um something super fancy suit and tie
kind of occasion if I had shorter hair I
would spike it up a little bit and have
like little
um little spikes going on but yeah so
I'm gonna add some heat to my hair and
see what we can go from there
so the reason why I'm adding heat to my
hair is because my hair was so flat that
I need to apply some heat to try to give
it some volume and direction for it to
go so that's why I'm applying some heat
as you can see just with the heat alone
I could hairspray this and then just
call it good honestly but uh we're not
doing that we're going to be using
pomade so I'm just going to start off
with just a little bit I'm gonna put it
in on my hands so a little hack with
hair product is that if you get a little
water and spray it
and your hands a little wet you can
apply it a lot easier to your hair
so for me my problem is mainly my sides
and they just want to poke out super
straight so
okay so with what I got going on with
how much product that I use
it's okay
it's it's pretty decent you know if
you're looking for some kind of
slickback hairstyle
um for me I like doing the 60 40 so
let's try that
okay so let's try that the 60 40 let's
push it back this way
and then let's get some volume going on
this if we can
again this is not the hair product that
you want to use for this hairstyle
um but I mean you can
but it's not going to be it's not gonna
it's not gonna hold that well right I
mean yeah it did it did okay it did okay
you see how my hair shine like it's wet
even when it's dry completely it's still
going to look like it's it's wet like
this so so this is what the high shine
looks like so we're going to go ahead
and just add a little bit more
the same amount
as last time so we're going to double
this up right we'll see what we can do
with double the hair product
this is just me but I like to try to get
as deep as I can to the roots so I scrub
it like shampoo into my scalp
okay so my hair
it looks like my hair wants to split
right here so we're gonna go ahead and
try to just uh enhance that and uh do a
60 40 split right there
so very high shine
very wet looking
and uh
feels really greasy right it feels
really greasy like my hands are shiny I
don't know if you can see that
but it literally
um
this would be a lot better for shorter
hair
and so just for fun we're gonna add
another a third amount
for the same amount
and we're gonna try to get this slicked
completely back okay
so with a third application of
pomade
you can see that my hair completely is
is okay to to slick back now so I have a
nice shiny slick back
here
Style
so this is the hairstyle that you're
looking for with the shine and you can
do and a slickback
this is the one for you so let me go
rinse this off start over from zero and
let's move on to the next one all right
and I'm back just wash my hair shampoo
there make sure all the products out I'm
gonna go ahead and dry it again and then
we'll start over
so now that we're back to the bowl cut
I'm going to add some heat push it back
a little bit make it a little easier to
style and then we'll move on to the
foaming cream
[Applause]
the foaming cream I don't know if you
can see that
but this one is definitely more of a
paste
it's uh very it's stickier as well
as you can see sticky but not like glue
so I've used this product in the past
before and I really do like it it's it's
not me personally I would prefer this
one over the Pomade just because Pomade
is not really my style that I go for
this one is a medium hold with a shine
but not a high shine so let's go ahead
and see what this one looks like
so just like last time we're going to go
ahead and apply
about a dime size
to
to use
I'm going to spray water with it
a little bit so it just spreads around
and
um
distributes
better
so here we go
so again for me my problem is my sides
so I like to add a little bit more to
the sides push it back a little bit more
and then for the top just evenly
distribute it out
so it looks like it must go for a middle
part so we're gonna try go ahead and try
a
middle part for this hair
product
we're just trying it out I don't know if
you guys gonna do a middle part but this
is just a middle part we're trying it
out here
okay
let's comb it up
okay so not too bad not too bad it looks
a little it doesn't have that really
high shine like it's wet but it does
have some kind of shine to it like you
can see in the light that there is a
little bit of shine to it but not as
much shine as the Pomade one I do like
this one a lot better because at least
my hair a lot more
um bouncy and it feels more
more doable if I was to wear this all
day okay so let's go ahead and try a
little bit more see what it looks like I
probably won't go for a third
application but maybe just uh the second
one just just to see where what happens
if we add a little bit too much so this
is double the amount that I'm using that
I would regularly use
I'm going to add it all over
and let's not do the middle part let's
do a uh let's do more like a comb over
huh so I'm going to push it over see if
we can get it to happen with with what I
was already trying to do
okay
so come this way
oh yeah
there's a lot of uh
a lot of pool
comb this this way like this
and then I get my handy dandy
comb all right part it out
Okay so
let's see
this would be
the idea
of a
comb over
add some value to let's add some volume
to the top
and uh let's see what it looks like
okay so it's not it's not bad
um this was able to
um
to hold my hair pretty well as you can
see these back pieces here they do want
to pop out because I don't have a lot of
hair product in the back that's mainly
in the front so they do want to pop up
but at least again it my hair looks more
natural it's a lot more bouncy
um it does have some volume to it and
it's not too bad if I was to wear this
hair I would actually hair spray a
little more hair a little hairspray and
add it to hold everything down but if I
didn't have hairspray this would be okay
where it's at
not bad
let's do the shake test because you know
um you might go to a rock concert and
you might want to shake your hair around
let's see how many times uh or what I
have to do to kind of mess up this
hairstyle okay
it actually made it look better
not bad it's still holding pretty good
and it can't complain you know it still
looks okay so that was the foaming cream
I'm gonna wash my hair again come back
dry my hair and then we'll move on to
the fiber all right
so we're back back to the bowl cut again
I'm gonna go ahead and dry my hair I'm
just going to go ahead and dry it
backwards that way we don't have to Two
Step dry okay and if you're wondering if
you should air dry or blow dry your hair
here's a link to that video
okay so it's pretty much dry and we're
gonna move on so the last product that
we are going to review is the fiber
again I thought this one's going to be
the hardest one to wash out but
um they've they're not that bad to wash
out you know a little shampoo and they
come out just fine but as you can see
this texture here is more like a clay
right so it's Clay
and let's see what shine this one has oh
that's a
that's all right
so fiber is a high hold and a low shine
all right so we'll see what that one
looks like
again hack spray your hand or get a
little wet and then mix it around a lot
better
this one's a little harder to spread if
you can see in the palm of my hand there
it's still a lot of product there but we
just keep mixing that out
so both hands are coated in the fiber
let's see how that applies on
okay
still got a little product in my hand
it's gonna keep going until it's all
gone probably apply it to my sides
oh yeah
slick that back baby
all right
so I do like the non-shine a really low
shine it looks like it's just naturally
stays up like this there is a little bit
of shine to it but it's not that bad and
uh yeah let's get to salvin
okay one thing I noticed right out the
back is because it is a high hold my
sides is like pasted down
which is not a bad thing but you just
don't want to look like you were pasted
your sides down
so make that look a little bit more
natural
okay
there we go all right all right so
there's a natural split right here down
the middle so we're gonna go ahead and
just do a uh
a part in the middle
and as you can see a lot of this doesn't
have product in that you know because
when you push it back it doesn't add the
product here
but which is okay you know you can add a
little bit more to it but if you want it
to be
um
a little less on top that's how you do
it not might look like Mickey Mouse
but it does hold my hair really good
though it does after my hair completely
dries and it goes for
um a few hours I can tell that it's
gonna sit just where I want it to go a
lot of this is going to fall down a
little bit I'll show you with a shake
test Shake test
foreign
now I really look like Mickey Mouse but
not bad it doesn't want to go past this
point
come one side back
and leave one side
kind of like hanging out there
something similar to this but not
exactly this but something similar to
this I want to try the
the comb over because this is actually
the product I use for the comb over but
I don't know if I can anymore with
this so I'm going to spray my hair with
a little bit of water so we can move it
around
and we'll go from there
okay not too bad
my hair is a little wet but that's fine
uh you you can let it dry and it'll stay
like this but what I want to do is I
want to achieve
this
comb over part
okay
I don't know if you can't or can't tell
but I mean I do have a light right here
so it's really bright but so it's if my
hair looks shiny it's because it's a
little bit of wet I sprayed it a little
bit but
um I do like this hold a lot better I
didn't have to use a lot
um like the the Pomade I had to use
three applications for my hair to be
completely pushed back with the foaming
cream I used two uh just to see how it
went and
um it really didn't hold my hair the way
I wanted to so I would go with the fiber
and all I would use this every day
honestly if you're looking for a product
that you can use every day I think that
the fiber is the one for you it's easy
to apply just wet your hand a little bit
smear it all over you know I call it
good and uh it's holding pretty well you
know toning pretty well
even though my hair is a little wet it's
not too bad so this is it for this video
let me know which one you like the most
and if there's anything that you guys
want me to review center my way and I'll
see what I can do this is Ming and I'm
out
[Music]
thank you